Testimony Time
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Lemlem Kassa, I am from the USA.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a tumour in my uterus.
The tumour in my uterus weighed 10 pounds and my legs weighed 28 pounds.
As you can see here, this was my belly and these were my legs.
There was fluid in my legs.
This was my tummy.
So you mean, what we are seeing on the pictures now
was your condition when you came to The SCOAN?
Yes.
And you were diagnosed of what problem?
A tumour in my uterus.
I had been to five different doctors who said that they had to cut me
from here to here to remove my uterus and everything.
I called my brother to pray for me and he said that I needed to go to Nigeria.
I didn't know anything about Emmanuel TV.
Then, I started watching Emmanuel TV and I saw miracle after miracle after miracle.
When I came here, I was privileged to meet with the man of God.
He opened the bottle of Anointing Water, sprayed it on me and prayed for me.
Then I went back.
When I checked with the doctor, they could not find the tumour in my uterus.
They found that it was out from my uterus.
So you mean, after the ministration of the Anointing Water by the man of God,
you went back and returned to the hospital for a checkup.
The doctor found out that the tumour was out of the uterus.
Correct.
You said you had a dream. Tell us when you had that dream and what it was about.
In that dream, the man of God came,
then he told one of the wise men to give him a razor.
One of the wise men gave him a razor, then he cut me across here.
He said there was nothing wrong with my uterus.
He pulled the whole, huge tumour from my uterus;
he took it out and threw it away.
Then, I woke up.
I went to the doctor and they said, "This is impossible.
How can it remove automatically?
This will be easy - we just have to cut it and take it out".
The same thing that the man of God did in the divine operation
was happening in the physical.
As you can see right here, the man of God cut me from here to here.
This is my uterus, as I told you.
The tumour was out of my uterus; it was right there.
Then in this one, this was the huge, big tumour that the man of God took and threw away.
It was the size of a human head as you can see.
When I was in recovery, my condition got very bad.
My blood pressure was 84 over 42 and I started leaking right here.
Then the man of God came to me in a dream with a designed cup.
On the cup was written, 'The joy of the Lord is our strength'.
He then said, "God is good. He's a stronghold to those who are in trouble.
He knows them, those who trust in Him".
He then gave me the cup, filled with a thick drink
and he told me to drink, that everything would be fine.
I drank it.
After that, I woke up and my blood pressure was 96 over 62 and the leaking stopped.
The next day, I was discharged.
As you see me now, my legs and body are not swollen.
I am in good health. Praise the Lord!
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus!
Wow, what God used the Anointing Water to do in her life!
The swollen tummy as a result of a tumour in the uterus was removed -
first in the dream by the man of God.
After the administration of the Anointing Water, she went back to the USA.
The man of God visited her in the dream, and carried out a spiritual surgery
and removed the tumour from her uterus.
After the doctors had tested her, they found out that the tumour was no longer in the uterus.
They discovered that the operation would now be easier.
By the time they did the surgery, exactly like what she saw the man of God
removing from her uterus in the dream, was what the doctor removed physically through surgery.
That we can see in the pictures on the screen of our television -
a huge tumour that almost consumed the life of this woman.
Since then, she is completely free.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus one more time!
Wow!
Evangelist, were you there when I came to her?
What a wonderful testimony!
She came from the USA purposely to share her testimony.
My advice to all women or anybody going through what I did
is that, there is hope in the Lord; don't lose hope.
Doctors can treat but Jesus Christ cures.
If He can do it for me, He will do it for you. Have faith in God.
When you received the Anointing Water, how did you minister it?
Because many don't know how to minister it.
They think they just have to open the bottle and drink it.
I took a lot of pictures of women with fibroids from YouTube,
from the Emmanuel TV testimonies.
I said, "If He can do it for them, He wil do it for me.
The God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, I have seen You doing miracles - the blind see,
so many, from A to Z, countless miracles - You will do it for me, in Jesus' name".
I ministered the Anointing Water with faith and the Lord did it.
But I am very sure you were praying, not saying words!
I fasted and prayed.
We salute your faith. Thank you very much.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.